Guide to the Stratemeyer Syndicate Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Printed Material, 1923-86; Series V; 0.25; (1 box)
  - Alger, Horatio, 1973, 1978, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 228)
  - Best seller lists, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 229)
  - Book reviews, 1973-87 (Box 9, Folder 230)
  - Children's literature, 1971-86, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 231)
  - Criticism, 1982 Apr 28 (Box 9, Folder 232)
  - Ghostwriters, 1980 Jul 7 (Box 9, Folder 233)
  - Legal cases, 1979-80 (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Libraries, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Mini Page [newspaper], 1977 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Miscellaneous references to Stratemeyer characters, 1970, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 237)
  - Nancy Drew, 1973-85 (Box 9, Folder 238)
  - Nancy Drew Reading Circle, 1973 Feb (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Newsboy [newsletter], 1976-78 (Box 9, Folder 240)
  - Post-Adams publishing, 1983-86 (Box 9, Folder 241)
  - Queries, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 242)
  - Satire, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 243)
  - Series literature, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 244)
  - Simon & Schuster purchase, 1984 Aug 4 (Box 9, Folder 245)
  - Squier, Edna, 1974 Apr 9 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Stratemeyer Syndicate, 1923-85 (Box 9, Folder 247-48)
  - Svenson, Andrew, 1975, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Television programs, 1977-82 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Testimonials, 1973, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 251)
- Notebooks, 1973-78; Series VI; 0.5; (1 box)
  Series VI consists of four notebooks written by Nancy Axelrad, and one (folder 256) by Kimberly Stratemeyer Adams.
  - Notebook, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 252)
  - Notebook, 1973-74 (Box 10, Folder 253)
  - Notebook, 1974-75 (Box 10, Folder 254)
  - Notebook, 1975-76 (Box 10, Folder 255)
  - Notebook, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 256)
- Oversize, 1927-84; 5.25; (3 boxes)
  Oversize papers contains materials from Series II, IV and V arranged in original order and two boxes which contain dictation machines.
  - Financial Documents
    - Finley, Kumble, Wagner, Heine, Underberg, Manley & Casey
      - Billing memorandum, 1984 Oct 9 (Box 11, Folder 257)
      - Client billing and payment history, 1984 Aug (Box 11, Folder 257)
    - Simon and Schuster
      - Accounts payable, 1984 Jul 19 (Box 11, Folder 258)
      - Distribution of proceeds from sale of partnership, 1984 Aug 17 (Box 11, Folder 258)
      - Proceeds available from sale of partnership, 1984 Jul 31 (Box 11, Folder 258)
      - Royalties receivable, 1984 Jul 19 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  - Other Papers
    - Authorship lists
      - Bobbsey Twins, 1950-84 (Box 11, Folder 259)
      - Hardy Boys, 1927-84 (Box 11, Folder 259)
      - Nancy Drew, 1930-84 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  - Printed Materials
    - Adams, Harriet; profiles, 1979 Apr 8 (Box 11, Folder 260)
    - Stratemeyer Syndicate, 1934-68 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  - Dictation machines
    - Lanier Edisette VIP with mini-cassette adapter, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 261)
    - Lanier Edisette VIP with footswitch and instruction booklet (Box 13, Folder 262)